<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Resistance</string>
    <string name="rules_of_the_game">
    Set in the near future, The Resistance pits a small group of 
    resistance fighters against a powerful and corrupt government.
    The resistance has launched a series of bold and daring missions 
    to bring the government to its knees. Unfortunately spies have 
    infiltrated the resistance ranks, ready to sabotage the carefully
    crafted plans. Even a single spy can take down a resistance
    mission team, choose your teams carefully or forever lose your 
    chance for freedom.\n

    \nThe Resistance is a game where players attempt to find out one
    another\'s identities, it is a game of social deduction and deception.\n

    \nThe game requires between five and ten players. In the game you are
    assigned 1 of 2 roles, a spy or a member of the resistance.
    Your role will be assigned when you and your friends press the 
    play button. Simply pass the phone accordingly, and be careful
    so that nobody sees your role.\n

    \nThe Spies are made aware of each others roles without the Resistance
    members knowing. This is done when a spy receives the phone, he can 
    see the list of all other spies.\n

    \nThe game consists of up to five missions. You can see the table of
    5 rounds during the team formation.\n

    \nAbout the team formation. Each mission has a leader. The leader
    proposes a mission team of a certain size, which the group approves
    by public vote.\n

    \nIf the group does not approve the mission by a simple majority,
    leadership passes to the next player.\n

    \nIf the leadership is changed more than 5 times, mission will be
    considered as failed, and it counts for the spies. 
    So be careful on the 5th switch of the captain.\n

    \nOnce a mission team formed, they vote whether the mission succeeds(passes)
    or fails.\n

    \nIf there are 6 or less players, it only takes one spy on a mission
    team to fail the mission. If multiple fails are carried out, only 
    one is counted. If three missions are successful, the Resistance wins.
    If three missions are failed, the spies win.\n

    \nIf there are 7 or more players, mission 4 will require 2 fails from
    spies to win the round. It is marked with a star * in the table.\n

    \nAfter a mission is completed, you can view its summary as a blinking
    blue or red colors. 1 blue indicates 1 players passing the mission, 
    1 red indicates that 1 spy failed the mission. That way you will able 
    to know number of passes and number of fails.\n

    \nAnd finally, the last, but most important rule of all:
    You are allowed to say anything, to anyone, at any time
    as long as it is said publicly.\n

    </string>
</resources>